<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humanrights | Psychologist Gopika Govindan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/humanrights/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/humanrights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Humanrights</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Humanrights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/humanrights/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Full-Circle Moment at the United Nations, Vienna</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/25_07_18_un_visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/25_07_18_un_visit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;max-width: 800px; margin: auto; text-align: justify; font-size: 1.05rem; line-height: 1.8;&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visiting the United Nations Office at Vienna (UNOV) 🌐 was more of a deeply personal highlight for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I would often listen in awe as my father shared stories of his work with the UN, particularly with WHO and UNICEF in the 1970s. His experiences painted vivid pictures of purpose, global cooperation and the impact of working for something greater than oneself. Those stories sparked a lifelong fascination in me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From learning about the work of organizations like UNODC, IAEA and UNIDO to engaging in thought-provoking discussions about peace, sustainability and global development, the experience left me with a deepened appreciation for multilateral collaboration and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The visit reminded me of the power of dialogue, unity and shared responsibility in addressing the challenges our world faces today from climate action to human rights and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🤝 Here is to generational inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🌐 Here is to purpose-driven work that transcends borders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grateful for this opportunity to visit and excited to bring these insights back into my own clinical work and mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
